You hold onto me.
I am protecting you.
The best storyline happens to me.
Choosing you and completing the task
are not related at all
This day
is the happiest day of my life so far
Ready, go
I really look forward to
getting in touch with you
I think it's not just about talking about life
The atmosphere is just right
What did you do at home today?
Then I made that beef noodle
and ate it all
I can make it again
I will make it again
Alright
I just wrote a short essay
The world of Truman is fake
but Truman is not
Maybe not perfect
but it's genuine
He is really straightforward
and very determined
I just want to ask you one question
Are you willing to
take a step forward
We announced that we are going to date
It's locked in
Soul is interesting
Free encounters
This program is played by young people
Soul APP
Exclusively sponsored broadcast
Global beauty and health products
On Watsons mini program
Thanks to healthy beauty, beautiful health
Jointly sponsored by Watsons
Hello
It's not bad, Brother
Brother Zhang is working on his form
Not the dimensions
You really know how to talk
Let me see what's going on
Let me take a look
My brother
Brother is slowly working out
Keep it up
Professional
Just help me lose weight, that's enough
Can you help me lose weight?
Alright, next time
I'll go to the study for a while
Why is it a bit cute?
I haven't seen your painting
I finished drawing this.
I already took it up.
Did you move my seat?
Because you are not
Don't you want others to see your painting?
Alright
You are being careful
A special date for him
That upward smile
Bro
The opportunity has come
The expression management is too poor
My heart is actually pounding
My first reaction was
A new female guest is coming
At that time, I felt like
I was unboxing a blind box
Then I thought it might be a
One-on-one date
Regarding this matter
I still have high expectations
Sneaked away
Acted very serious
Started running
He was waiting for this day, right?
He ran so fast he was slipping all the way
Yes
Just like our cat
Going or not? Let's go
Something came up
Something came up, you guys go ahead
Okay
I'll come back and play with you
He hurriedly changed into a new suit.
Bro, I'm back in action.
I've revived again.
Why is the inner monologue you gave him so funny?
Where are you going?
This is...
Going out for a bit.
Why?
Very mysterious.
What's going on?
Going out for a bit.
Have fun.
Suit, Brother Luo.
How is it? Does it have a youthful vibe?
Goodbye.
You're going out.
He really can't keep things to himself.
Look at his face.
So cute.
Why is it a man? (voice)
It's you again
We have a date
Could they have a date?
Why is he here again?
It's them again
This is so embarrassing.
You are going out.
He also received this.
Why is he sneaking around?
Yeah, and he's carrying slippers.
He probably doesn't want Liang Tian to know he's going out.
You go out
He laughed awkwardly
Brother Zhang also received it
He also received it
Everyone received it
No one is left
So funny
What's going on
It's you again
We have a date
Really special
I think this date is really special
And you need me to keep this a secret
What do we have to keep secret
Alright, that's it
He was very disappointed
Does this count as a date
The most surprising moment
Was seeing Lao Luo's back for the first time
That was too conflicting
It's like you're imagining a girl
Waiting for you at the corner
A very broad back
He's right in front of you
A broad back
Xiao Su was really disappointed
Then guess
Do you think the one who came is really a singer?
Not necessarily
How can you be sure it is
someone new coming?
Because
I heard your voice a long time ago
Brother Zhang
No way
Three men, one show
No
The moment I heard your voice
I was a bit disappointed
I was just sitting here
I heard him come
I was already surprised
Then you walked out from there
I think that's it
I'm used to it
There might be more later
I said you would come
Look at this
Didn't expect it, right?
I feel like I've been deceived
I totally feel the same
I even pretended to be mysterious with you
Saying I need to step out for a bit
And we ended up meeting here
The last one, sit down
This is too funny
Everyone is here
How did you feel when you came in?
So what's the situation?
Do you know?
No idea
But it's a bit strange
The seats
How come
There are only two chairs on this table
I feel like there's some kind of rule
So excited
The answer should be revealed soon
Everyone is here
What exactly is it?
What?
Choose anything, sing anything.
Okay.
See if anyone can sing.
Let's get some first, come on.
Men's karaoke room.
Brother Zhang, I think you should sing Andy Lau
It should sound great
He is singing with his eyebrows
They are all karaoke kings
Luo Junfan's expression
This expression is really amazing
I want to use Mr. Luo's expression as an emoji
I like your poetry recitation
Poetry recitation
Too bad
Thank you all for your tolerance
My singing
Really isn't something people can listen to
It's okay
You look good, just standing there looking good is enough
Spare me, please
Okay, I'll give it a try
Not too high
How clear my sky is
Transparent promises
Are the air of the past
Here they come.
It feels very beautiful
Looking forward to it
Where did they go?
So pleasing to the eye.
We are here too.
Is it this place?
Holding hands
So beautiful
So pretty
What does this mean?
I will start a "special date"
A newcomer is coming
Xia Xia
Let's go
Caught off guard
How do we sit here?
Anyway, let's sit down first
Let's sit like this for now
Four cups
We should sit according to this
So, here's the question.
Today is a date for the four of us, right?
But it's also possible
because it's a special date.
Yes.
I see.
This is getting interesting.
Maybe it feels like no one will come.
They might be hiding somewhere.
Why does he look quite handsome?
Let's see his face.
Such a high feeling
He must be very tall
Hello
The eyes flashed
Hello everyone
Hello
Why are your eyes fixed?
Because actually we have one more boy
Then when another boy appeared
I was stunned at that moment
I didn't expect it to be
a new boy joining
I am very happy
I am looking forward to meeting the new friend
Because I seem to be the first to see him
Because he walked over from the opposite side
He is very tall and handsome
And his shoulders are broad
The first impression is
it feels like you've practiced.
Practiced.
This overwhelming sense of security.
My name is Wan Xiao.
I think love
is definitely a necessity in life.
I don't think anyone
can restrain their longing for love.
My most romantic imagination of love
is probably
being able to hold hands with someone you really like
and see the world together.
Quite handsome.
A sporty vibe.
Hello everyone.
Sit.
I'll get a chair.
Okay.
So you want to sit
You can choose yourself.
I'll sit
I'll sit in the middle.
Alright.
Hello everyone
My name is Wan Xiao
You can call me Wan Wan
Or you can call me Xiao Ge
Either is fine
Xiao Ge
I would like to know your names
Try to start as many conversations as possible
Because it's a great opportunity
I can
get to know all four girls at once
Tian Er
Yes
Xia Xia
Wo Wo
Ka Ka
Impressive
Applause
Alright, that's fine
Where are you from?
I'm from Beijing, yes
Are you working in Hangzhou now?
Or somewhere else?
Working in Shanghai
I work in Beijing
Working in Beijing
Yes, I came from Beijing
What about you?
Us?
Take a wild guess
Go ahead, guess
I'm really bad at guessing
You
Wait a moment
You're from the northeast
Yes
Look
Exposed
You're a bit hard to guess
From the south
Not from the south
From the north
I am from Xinjiang
From Xinjiang
I really can't guess this one.
Doesn't she look like it?
She looks so much like it.
Indeed, when you put it that way.
She does have a Xinjiang style.
That's so funny.
Actually, she's from Inner Mongolia.
Really?
You're not tricking me, right?
Where is it exactly?
It's from Hubei.
From Hubei, okay.
Guess.
Just guess once.
Only one chance.
Hangzhou.
Northeast.
Tell us the reason.
Feels like the vibe matches Hangzhou.
Quite fashionable.
Thank you.
Alright, it's my turn.
Shanghai.
Why did you guess it right away?
It really fits Shanghai.
The fashionable style of the magic city.
Thank you, teacher.
You speak so well.
We Beijingers are good at talking.
This scene of me with four girls
having a meal together
is definitely a first in my life
I've never felt so surrounded before
To be honest
facing four girls alone
even if it's not an interrogation
I would still feel quite pressured
Can you tell me
what your profession is?
Profession? I'm in the internet industry
Then you're in the same field as Lao Luo
Yes
Lao Luo, right?
He's a guy
Yes
Okay, I'll remember this name
I'll get to know Lao Luo when I go back
What are your hobbies?
What do you think my hobbies are?
Just from appearance
Sports, fitness
Yes, I also think it's sports
Yes, I've been into fitness for eleven years
Then you really are like Hou Chengjie
Your shoulders do look quite broad
Really?
We can spar a bit
I have already started imagining that scene.
I can't stop myself from imagining it.
Two people are
Yes
The famous scene from last season is about to reappear.
So, may I ask how much you can lift with one hand?
How much with one hand?
How much weight can you lift?
Getting serious now.
If it's a dumbbell,
Fifty or sixty kilograms should be no problem.
Over a hundred pounds.
A dumbbell over a hundred pounds.
How did Hou Chengjie ask him that day?
Was it a hundred kilograms?
Yes
Pupils
Pupils shaking
A hundred kilograms
Directly lose
Are you curious about him?
We invited a
wrestler to come over.
He is so funny.
One hundred kilograms.
Just a brief interlude.
Okay.
Tomorrow is New Year's Eve.
Yeah.
Brother Zhang at first
Brother Zhang said he wanted to make dumplings today.
Sure.
Do you know how?
Actually, I don't.
I can do it.
Other than dumplings, what else?
What dish are you good at?
Actually, basically not too complicated ones.
I can make anything with a recipe.
Great, that's wonderful.
That's great.
Everyone can cook.
Can everyone cook?
I've done it many times.
I usually eat at home.
Xiao Hu thought,
Luckily, I made beef noodles yesterday.
That's not acceptable.
I still want to eat his beef noodles.
No matter what, I must make him cook a bowl for me.
No matter what.
Just like that
Yesterday we just broke a record
Tomorrow it's your turn to break it
What record are we breaking?
It's about eating the most in the cabin
Delicious food
Okay
So delicious
Absolutely
Liang Tian is even more excited
Teacher Luo ate three bowls
How could it not be delicious?
I think these past two days
Looking at Yunting, I have a feeling
He doesn't seem real
Yes
Being this handsome
Is just absurd
Really handsome
This is
Yunting
It's beef noodles
Beef noodles
Code name: Beef noodles
Visual impact
So much pressure
Before this
I knew nothing about this cabin
But through everyone's introduction
I might feel some pressure too
But
I should find some small opportunities
To showcase some of my charm
Very beautiful
So cute
My name is Yan Xing, I am twenty-nine years old
I feel half-mature
That's pretty much my current state
I've grown a lot compared to before
But I wouldn't say I'm completely mature yet
My ideal romantic life
The core is in each other's lives
Adding the finishing touch
This girl's face has a bit of a first love feeling
Hello
Where should I sit?
I'll get another chair.
This is prepared for you, right?
Actually,
Aren't you singing?
Keep singing.
I chickened out.
I don't dare to embarrass myself in front of experts.
I'm not.
Suddenly, no one dared to sing.
Afraid to sing.
You put too much pressure on me.
It's my turn now.
Feels like it's going to be explosive.
I feel the same way.
No.
I'm just at an average karaoke level.
She started singing right away, can you imagine?
Really.
Very poised.
She went to sing one-on-five.
But she didn't seem too nervous.
Very confident.
The first impression is
a bit assertive.
Wanting to take control.
Feels like a big change is coming.
Can you make it louder?
I'll adjust it for you.
Thank you.
You try it
Okay
Do you need help adjusting this?
Thank you
My impression of Su Yonghao is
I think he is very enthusiastic
A really warm-hearted guy
He is a sunshine boy
Yes
Let's move this first
Sorry
There are a lot of things
A considerate boy
Okay
Oh no, you saw what I'm going to sing
I don't know
I didn't know she was going to sing "Compromise"
I'm not really sure
So nervous!
I've heard this before
Good
Thank you all
New friends have the chance to sing two songs
You really know how to offend people
Want to hear more
No, the first song is just to get familiar
Warm up the voice
You mean I didn't warm up my voice
No
There are also times he can't catch up
My first Waterloo, Brother Hou
Yeah
I'll punish myself with a drink
When I first saw her
I thought she was quite pretty
Her smile was very big
I felt she might be a sweet girl
Because she always had that smile
A rather outgoing and lively personality
Tall
A slim girl
An interesting soul
Just be good friends
Or be a
Just
buddy
get along like this
I think it's more comfortable this way
Yes
What's the new friend's name
What's your name
My name is Yan Xing
Yan as in color
Xing as in bank
Yan Xing
Yan
There are few people with the surname Yan
Yes
So what do you do
Is it related to music
I work in social media
And you
I'm Su Yonghao
You can call me John
Su Yonghao
I need to remember it all at once now
Five people's names?
It's okay.
Not remembering is just a punishment.
It's fine.
My name is Luo Junfan.
Luo Junfan.
You don't have to make it so complicated.
You can just call me Luo.
Remembering one character is enough.
Hu Yunting.
Gu Yue Hu.
The "Yun" from "allow."
The "Ting" from "family."
So, how old do you think he is?
He is the youngest among us.
2001 2002 2003
Half-cooked
I guessed too low
Thank you
Too supportive
Yes, he's from 1997
Not 1979 or 1980
Heard of it, never seen it
No
It should be 1979 here
You don't need to say anymore
Some things we both know
But saying it out loud is a bit offensive
Yes
So who do you think is next
I'm the youngest
Then who is the most mature
Definitely the one from 1979
I'm the oldest, right
Don't touch me.
It's okay.
Just kidding.
The answer is revealed.
I was born in 1994, 30 years old.
Born in 1994, 30 years old.
You really don't look it.
Really don't look like you were born in 1994.
Okay, continue.
I
At forty, I have no doubts
You can't tell at all
Yes
Chinese is truly profound
I really couldn't tell the previous one
And I really couldn't tell this one
Really
The characters are the same
But the meanings are really
vastly different
Reflect if it's your own problem
Still arguing
When you guess me
Just guess smaller and you'll be right
Everyone wants to guess correctly
The desire to win is very strong
You go first.
It's time for revenge.
Since you treated me like that just now,
18 (years old)
Your emotional intelligence is really high.
You are very good with words.
My impression of Lao Luo
I think he is more like
the life of the party in a crowd.
Because I have always teased him.
I was joking with him.
Wherever he is,
no one feels awkward.
When meeting new friends,
I don't feel awkward at all.
It's very comfortable.
I can't guess.
Can't guess.
It's okay, just guess.
Just guess.
28 (years old)
29 (years old)
That's right.
Really.
The year 1995.
Thank you for guessing a bit younger.
Come on, let's have a toast.
Welcome.
Nice to meet you all.
Nice to meet you.
Okay
There's really a message
Let me check first
It's mine (phone rings)
Hold on
When I received this
message about a one-on-one with the girl
it was actually quite good
it was a great opportunity
to further
get to know everyone better
soon I have to choose one
yes, face to face
so fast
because I know
if I choose Lao Luo
we will definitely have a great conversation
if I talk to him
we will never let the conversation drop
but
I want more
to get to know Xiao Hu better
because he does look quite unique
so I have always
between him and Lao Luo
been thinking
He received it
Your date is over
Log off immediately
Is it singing from above or below?
Singing from above.
No chance to listen anymore.
You can return to the cabin.
No chance to listen.
Such a cruel feeling.
What are you going to do?
Are we retreating?
Yes.
Let's go.
See you later.
Next, it's your time.
It should be Xiao Hu
He sat down
I am also leaving
She is
She wants to understand
Teacher Luo
Because I am actually a
I might need others more
to bring up topics
I think Lao Luo and I
are actually on the same wavelength
I find his words very funny
we can chat together
there's a lot to talk about
just when I was still a bit hesitant
the Soul App's adventure bell
matched me with him
Chosen Lao Luo
Sure enough, his opportunity has come
Lao Luo, do your best
You
I think Teacher Luo will like it
Yes, she looks sweet on the outside
But inside, she seems like a mature woman
Yes
Actually, I was stunned at that moment
I was just dumbfounded
Because I felt
I wasn't ready for a one-on-one
To go on a date with a new guest
Goodbye
Have fun
You feel now
Happiness came too suddenly, right?
Have fun
Okay, goodbye, see you at the cabin
See you at the cabin
Goodbye
Time passed quickly today
But I also brought you a small gift today
As a conclusion
Encounter Bell
Thank you
Actually, I think
We should thank the Encounter Bell from the Soul APP more
Why
The Encounter Bell is really effective
It allowed us to meet
And I look forward to
Having more interactions in the cabin
Sure
Back home again.
Guess what they are doing.
Did they all go out?
Really not here.
Their shoes are not here either.
Seems like no one is home.
Yes, it's so quiet.
Someone should be in the media room.
I guess they all went out.
Maybe they have guys too.
Hello.
Did you bring a new girl back?
No.
She and the guy behind her.
Brought a new girl back.
Two who are working are at home.
Three of us are at home.
And then Tiantian and that guy.
What do you mean?
What do you want to hear?
Anything is fine.
So, Sister Tian stayed.
The new guy chose Tian Tian.
Liang Tian.
Yes.
Should I sit across from you?
Sure.
Sit across from me.
Liang Tian's words are
that the first impression is very
straightforward
generous, sunny, and cheerful
I would feel that she
herself
whether it's her experiences or her personality
are things I am willing to understand more deeply
Come, have some
Do you usually eat desserts?
I do
Although I control it
I still eat when I should
Because I feel that you usually
probably also control your sugar intake or something
I do control
sugar intake
Me too
I rarely eat this kind of dessert
Back then, my mom tried to control my weight
She wouldn't let me eat it
When I was a child
I felt monitored
Do you think after going to college
You escaped that monitoring?
Living in the dorms over there
Relatively speaking
You become more independent
And more free
What is your major?
German
Studying German
Yes
I'm really curious
What has everyone been doing these past two days?
These past two days
These past two days, we
The time we gather the most
Is when we cook and eat
And usually, what everyone does the most
When we get together
Is, for example, singing together
And then
There is a male guest named Yonghao
He brought a guitar
Then everyone can play
Then everyone sings
It sounds quite joyful
Yes
There is someone in a sports-related field
Xiao Hou
He trains to be particularly strong
He doesn't have thin muscles
But his shape is well-trained
Also very flexible
Very beautiful
So that's how it is
Then another one
Who likes to work out frequently
Named Zhang Chenxi
Brother Zhang wore a tank top today for the first time
I took a look
Brother Zhang has thin muscles
So, do you like lean muscles
or do you prefer big muscle mass?
I like lean muscles.
You like lean muscles.
It's not about liking or disliking.
As long as there are muscles,
they all look pretty good, right?
It seems many people like fitness.
Male guests.
Yes, actually boys.
Including me, three.
The boys are quite active.
After listening to Liang Tian's introduction
there is some pressure
but I think I have my own advantages
I'll arrange a practice with them tomorrow
Yes
You can spar with each other
The cabin has beautiful scenery again
You can see it
It's still interesting to enter the cabin
After you go in
you will feel very relaxed
because everyone is very nice
Looking forward to it
There is someone named Wan Xiao
He's a guy
Yes
The new guy who arrived today also works out
And his shoulders look broad
But I don't know what he looks like
What does he do for a living
Operations
Internet operations
Yes, managing some accounts and such
Our girl also works in social media
How old is she
29 years old
She is the only one among our girls
Who is under 30 years old
Yes
I have some things to do
I'll leave first
I am still busy
I'll go first
Look, this is where everyone lives
Everyone lives on the second floor
All live on the second floor
Bringing the newcomer
Why are you still eating
Hello everyone
Is this a sense of crisis?
This is a new friend
Wait a moment
Hello everyone
Hello
Then I'll bring him in
See you in a bit
See you soon
I'll go upstairs to change my vest first
Male competition
She is so funny
How does she feel
She is very suitable to sit in our place
Observation room
I really want to see it
I also want to be the main female character
Just to experience male competition
Hello
Welcome
The new guy is quite handsome
He dresses very formally
He has a boss-like vibe
Hello everyone
Hello
So tall
Why is everyone so tall
Yes, each one is taller than the last
Yes
I really have to look up
(to see) the top of his head
When I saw him today, I asked
I asked how tall he is
After he answered
I said okay
He might be the tallest in the house now
191 cm
He is taller than Xiao Hu
So much pressure
I think 180 cm is already tall
There are people taller than you
Taller than me
He has that domineering CEO vibe
At that moment, I felt a bit
A bit abrupt
Also a bit
Defensive
Did the iconic scene come so quickly?
Does our new friend know our names?
Probably not.
Yes.
Didn't she introduce us once already?
She did introduce us once.
But did he match the names?
You can guess again.
I know Brother Zhang and Yunting.
It means you didn't introduce us.
I did introduce.
Introduced.
Turns out we are so insignificant.
We are not worthy of you remembering our names.
Brother Chen
This Yonghao
Yonghao
Then this little Hou
Little vest
Yes, I just remember the little vest
So should I call you
Little Wan or Old Wan
Call me Little Wan
Little Wan
Wan Wan is really good at cooking, right?
Not particularly skilled
Just enjoys doing it
So his cooking skills
It might be a challenge for you
You are now good at stirring things up
You now
No
You are very bad now
You have learned to be bad
They started
What else do you like
I also like fitness
Male competition
What is she doing
She is so funny
Quick, are you hot
I think you are hot
This is also very wide.
How tall are you?
191 cm
Then you are the tallest.
So high
This is a bit thrilling
Back
Brought a girl back
What are they doing?
It's so lively.
Hello.
We meet again.
So soon.
Welcome new partner.
Hello.
Hello, welcome.
You're back.
Hello.
So sweet.
You all look so beautiful.
My first impression of Yanxing was
that she is a quiet and sweet girl.
And her smile is just
very comforting.
This girl looks gentle and soft
She has a personality
completely different from mine
I feel like I'm rough and careless
But I feel this new girl
is very delicate and meticulous
And then
She is very petite
and graceful
You chat with them for a while
I'll go check where my room is
Okay
He really looks like a little kid
He came with his little blanket
Yes
This is mine
Sorry, I didn't know
Sit
Okay
What are they doing sitting there
I don't know
Can you play this
I can play
Liang Tian is really tired of asking
But he doesn't play well
Come, try it
Come on, try it
Are you going to flip the table?
Don't you dare.
What are you doing?
Are you really going to flip the table?
Flip the table.
Wait a moment.
Impressive.
It's okay.
Alright.
Sit down.
Go for it.
Won.
You won.
Lie down in a row.
What's up?
You guys are taking a break.
We can directly update to F6.
Our F5.
F5.
Half-cooked House F5, quickly.
We are Half-cooked House F5.
Lie down quickly, go.
Three, two, one, go.
Can't fit.
Squeeze in, it's possible.
That's too ridiculous.
Just squeeze in.
I find it very funny.
The width of the two of them is just
taking up one sofa.
Then the rest just squeeze in.
What kind of scene is this?
Let's update the script today.
Just say we are Half-cooked House F6.
We are their
animal clowns
You are just a part of our game
Yes, a part of the game
Yes
Come on
Okay, three, two, one
We are
Half-cooked House F6
It's really embarrassing, really embarrassing
It's really ridiculous
You guys make up for it, you
Let's start the introduction
Introduce
Let them integrate quickly
Come
Let's play the old game again, okay?
How about blindfolding?
Okay?
Is it okay?
Yes
Because last time I wasn't blindfolded
Last time it was just me and Brother Zhang
Yes
Then let's start with you two
Blindfold, blindfold my brother
Ask yourself
Will you introduce?
No introduction
Introduction
Wowo
I
Full name
Don't know
Ren Jiabi
Thank you
This suspense is intense
So reliable
Then she worked in the finance industry
Actually, she didn't originally work in finance
She originally worked in
It's called
No need to trouble yourself, Zhang
Are you really troubling yourself like this?
No
He likes to challenge himself
No, this is a top student's self-demand
What's that management called
It's called arts management
Yes
Right?
Alright, it's over
Close your eyes
Come on
Introduce or not
Introduce
This handsome guy
This is mine
There's nothing to introduce
Just say it directly
You saved his life yesterday, that's it
No
She didn't save my life
She is the girl I have a crush on
This overwhelming sense of security
Take this difficult question and answer it yourself
Don't make the girl feel troubled
It's not that she saved my life
She is the girl who makes my heart flutter
Your level is too low.
Mr. Hou, and then he is
how to introduce
in great shape
you have a chance to take a look
take a look
it's a room
take a look at this room
open it and see it's a washboard
yes
and then further understanding is needed
because he actually came quite late, yes
you don't understand yet
I understand, I understand
starting to act cute
I'm still stuck at the visit part
have you guys gone this far already
visit the room
I'm done with the introductions.
Cover your eyes, I'll point.
Should we introduce him?
Sure.
Forget it.
Just drop it.
Let me hear how you introduce.
Luo Junfan.
Luo what?
Junfan.
It's fine.
You don't need to waste time on me.
Profession is a...
Online sales person.
A rough yet precise feeling
You can't say it's wrong, right?
Finished
The segment is over
No longer needed
There is some truth to that
Wait a moment
What will happen between Yuan Chengjie and me in the future
No
Yuan Chengjie
We hurt each other
Come on
How will Hou Chengjie and I get along in the future
Ask
Ask the "Book of Answers"
Accept some changes
Accept some career changes, right?
The vocabulary is really good
Hu
I have a reason for liking you
Because I don't talk
Just kidding
Next, it's your turn
Can you introduce me now?
What's the name again?
Deduct points
Called Yan Xing
Yan as in color
Xing as in bank
Year 1995
And then
Not very accurate at judging people
Easily sees people as older
I want to know how old she guessed you today
Anyway, older than Zhang Ge
No, older than Zhang Ge
Zhang Ge
Why did you bring up Zhang Ge
Brother
Who is targeting my brother
I will be the first to get angry and disagree
Initially, I was a little nervous
but seeing everyone chatting happily
made me feel
very relaxed, everyone is great
I'm really looking forward to life in the cabin
No, she has a good eye for you
I'm glad to have met many new friends
I think everyone is excellent
And they also have rich experiences
There will be many topics to talk about
My name is Johnny
My name is Jonas
Nice to meet you
Do you speak German?
A little bit
I wanted to go there for a working holiday before
So I studied for a year
I also have a feeling
This trip
Will be very, very unforgettable
There is news
Tomorrow, the Half-Cooked Cottage will welcome New Year's Eve
Everyone will prepare the New Year's Eve party themselves
Countdown together
I don't have any particular talent
Yes, me neither
You perform something for them
That simple sketch
One stroke and then draw a Riverside Scene at Qingming Festival
That kind
Perform that
How about the washboard abs trick
I've heard of it
Never seen it
You can sing
I can tell a joke
That's not necessary
Not necessary
I can sing my own single
Really?
I can adapt it
I think this New Year's Eve will be an opportunity
I look forward to more interactions with people I like
Are you singing tomorrow?
You play, I sing
Okay
This New Year's Eve for me
is actually very meaningful
Playing and singing with someone I like
is a wonderful thing
At the moment when the new year arrives
I especially hope to be with
someone I like
to welcome this moment together
Make her breakfast
How nice
A new day has begun
This smells amazing!
It smells so good.
Yes
I was going to suggest cooking century egg and lean pork congee
Smelling this
This smells so good.
Old Hu cooked beef again.
It smells amazing.
I can smell it from upstairs.
He didn't forget her beef noodles.
So fragrant.
When I got up today
I hurried to make a bowl of beef soup
Last time I made beef soup
Liang Tian didn't get to eat it
I made that beef noodle
It was all eaten
All the beef was eaten
But the soup is still there
It can be made again
I will make it again
Alright
So I wanted to say today
I especially want to make this bowl (of beef noodles)
Reliable Xiao Hu
Is there beef noodles
Didn't purchase today
No ingredients
Make it tomorrow
Alright
He should make it very delicious, right?
She should be happy to eat the first bowl, right?
It looks so fragrant
Really good
Liang Tian was always by the side
This is the soup, right?
The noodles are not cooked yet
Not cooked yet
Eat a little first
Too much
Thank you
It's very hot
Quite happy
According to our previous
agreements, it seems
it should be the night of the 31st
after finishing the procurement and coming back
but I really didn't expect
he did it during the day on the 31st
he just wanted
to let me eat this bowl of noodles quickly
He is expressing his initiative in his own way.
How nice.
This would be perfect with some noodles.
Is it delicious?
Delicious.
This is incredibly fragrant.
I had three bowls that day.
Teacher Luo still came to eat.
This soup.
Isn't it?
Perfect.
This must be delicious.
It looks very fragrant.
Student Xiao Luo.
Why are there only mushrooms and potatoes?
An avalanche occurred.
No snowflake is innocent.
Don't just ask me.
So, there's no meat?
Just a bowl of soup is enough.
No, I have food.
Come on.
No, I won't eat.
Are you disgusted with me?
I hope you eat a bit more.
No, really.
I can go out to eat later.
Can you play badminton with me?
Sure, okay.
Always wasting time on someone like me.
On someone unimportant.
I still remember your incredibly sweet smile.
Do you want to be hurt badly?
No, I don't.
Don't be like this.
What do you mean?
I know.
Someone's heart is going to break.
What's wrong?
Ren Jiabi didn't take it.
Does she not know or...
Whose is this?
Who is J?
Xiao Jie.
I heard the sound of glass breaking.
Did she not see it when she went out?
Yes.
Did you see this?
She didn't take it.
She actually didn't take it.
Let me analyze it for you.
She definitely couldn't find it.
Why?
Because she has high emotional intelligence.
People with high emotional intelligence
will always eat no matter what.
No matter the situation.
So she definitely couldn't find it.
Yes, I said
I said you should take it out and throw it away
About this interesting breakfast incident
It was really a huge misunderstanding
Because on the first day when he put the breakfast
He said the breakfast was in the fridge
So I naturally
Went to check the fridge
In the evening, I told him
I said I go to work every day
Quite early
Then I said after you finish at night
You still have to prepare this breakfast
It's quite tiring
You don't have to keep doing it
Then the note on the second day changed to say
Remember to eat breakfast
I thought
That should mean although
You don't need me to make breakfast for you
But you should remember to eat breakfast yourself
So the next day
I naturally assumed
There was no breakfast
A beautiful misunderstanding
It's okay
I won't make it for her anymore
It's over, it's already broken, broken
Don't break
It hurts to see it
I still remember your incredibly sweet smile
Why is it so heartbreaking
Shopping buddies, let's go
Let's go
I just happen to have an appointment with Liang Tian
She wants to sing her own song
Then I said, how about I accompany you?
And she wants to lower the key
Lowering it by two keys is quite difficult to handle
I'll just rearrange it for you
He is taking this matter very seriously
Old Su
I want to go out and buy fireworks later
Do you want to go?
I don't think I'll make it
Okay, you need to practice singing, right?
Yes, because she wants to lower it by two keys
Tian's one, right?
Yes
Okay
When do you plan to go out?
Planning to spend a
Let's see when you're ready
Going alone is very lonely
I'm afraid six o'clock might be too late
It will be a bit late
I'll do it right away
But I probably won't be that fast
Okay, you go ahead
Ask me again in half an hour
Okay
Thank you
Apparently, he has been composing this piece all along.
Went to watch the sunset.
She didn't ask either.
At that time
he was seriously transcribing music for Teacher Liang
actually, he had mixed feelings inside
I always felt
he might have some affection for me
so I guess I was testing him
because he also said
he said, why not wait until he finishes transcribing
so I thought this was also a signal
Yonghao
Have you finished peeling?
Only halfway
Then I'll go by myself
Okay
Okay, be careful on the road
Because I'm really not that fast
Understood
You go ahead
Safe travels
His feelings for Liang Tian are very clear.
He is quite brave.
I'm home.
I did something.
Happy.
Let's go.
I'm back.
You guys are back from shopping.
Yes.
There are a bit too many things.
Put them in the kitchen first.
It's so late.
If you're not brave, you'll miss out on fate.
Only you two are left.
Why?
Fireworks.
They brought the fireworks back.
I've been practicing the score all day.
You need to listen to the song in G and T keys.
Then think about it yourself.
How does it sound when it's lowered by two degrees?
It's so difficult.
Do you want to try?
You can try.
Let's go, I'll listen to it.
You're too difficult.
It's too difficult.
You didn't help me at all.
Impressive
So we directly lowered the pitch
Great teamwork
Easy
I am a musician
It's quite captivating, isn't it?
Yes
I've been thinking about this all day
You should sing this tonight
Yes, because this is the program we prepared
Yes, I need to rehearse with him
Brother, let's rehearse together
Okay, sure
Exceptional charisma, great energy
We always think of life too negatively
The atmosphere during practice
Makes me feel
I've already entered a Spring Festival Gala rehearsal
Reach out
Regarding this talent show
Of course, I'm looking forward to it
More interaction with Liang Tian
So I'll complete this song with her
I'll be quite happy
It's New Year's Eve
So excited
Okay
What we are seeing now is
their preparations for New Year's Eve
all the preparations
But actually, up until now
our little house has five women and six men
Yes
And I think everyone should
clearly feel the undercurrents
The most obvious pair is Liang Tian and Teacher Su
Yes
Xiao Hu
And just now, Hou Chengjie
He, for the first time in front of everyone
proactively said this is the girl I have feelings for
At that moment, my first thought was
it was meant for the girl
and my second reaction was
it was meant for the other guy to hear
This girl has already been chosen by me
Yes
So there was a bit of
undercurrents
visible currents
The currents are surging
I think
The atmosphere in our small cabin
has a small detail
when newcomers integrate
they especially take care of the newcomers' feelings
whether everyone in the new environment
is equally well taken care of
such reassuring moments
can be shared with us
I think every moment of my work
is still the same
I am shy on the show
but every time the regular teachers
see me not talking
they mention me
this makes me feel very reassured
I thought of another
when I was taken care of by a friend
my first time fishing
she often goes sea fishing
she would tell me
you need to take seasickness medicine on the boat
then she kept using a card camera and a phone
constantly taking pictures of me
from various angles
tirelessly taking pictures of me
At that time, I was really soft-hearted
Also, I am participating in a show recently
I told her that I am participating in this show
Then she said
Give me your address
I'll send you some clothes
I want you to look better
Yes, to look better
And usually, regarding outfits
Some tips and insights
We will also talk about them
I think friends like this are really
In the early days, I was in a new environment
and really needed the company of someone familiar.
I worked behind the scenes for many years,
but actually, I am a new singer.
Once on a stage,
with my big brother Chen Chusheng,
before he went on stage,
he would give me a lot of encouragement.
He said, "Do you know,
the song we are performing today
is written by you?
Such a beautiful song,
don't you want everyone
to enjoy it with you?
Of course, while letting others enjoy it,
you should be the first to enjoy it.
Sing this song on stage
and don't let nervousness come first.
Today, I will be with you,
let's sing this song well together.
Don't think about anything else."
That's great.
Actually, have you noticed
that besides being clueless about love,
Mr. Luo
is very supportive when new people appear.
He is very good at backing them up.
Yes.
In a new environment,
he actually thrives.
I just hope that in the next episode,
we can see
progress like Mr. Luo's.
Fill up this little notebook a bit more.
Like these sun types and moon types.
Learn them all.
Sun plus moon equals bright.
So your tomorrow will be better.
Alright, Teacher Luo?
And next time,
don't just show your cuteness.
Learn from anyone.
You're here to fall in love, Teacher Luo.
Keep it up.
So funny.
Sent out wonderful blessings